Contact

balwant.n82@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Antivirus · Information
Technology · System
Administration · IT Management
· Telecommunications · Vendor
Management · DNS · Active
Directory · Windows Vista ·
Microsoft Exchange

Accomplishments · See all 1 Language

Balwant Singh

Lead Technical Support at REVE Systems New Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

8+ Year of experience in IT industries and having good experience of Pre-sales, Post-sales, POC, Demo, Technical Training, Cybersecurity Analytic, Product Implementation, IT infrastructure operation, Technical Support, IDS/IPS, Firewall, Antivirus and End point protection. Skilled in Windows, MAC, Linux, Active Directory, DNS, DHCP and Networking.

Experience

Lead Support Engineer · REVE Systems

December 2018 - Present · New Delhi Area, India

Lead Suport Engineer · Quick Heal Technologies L.L.C.

March 2013 - Present · New Delhi Area, India

System Engineer · Tulip Telecom

February 2010 - Present

System Engineer · Dolphin Computers

October 2007 - January 2010 (2 years 4 months) · New Delhi

System Engineer · Nexus Computer

November 2005 - September 2007 (1 year 11 months) · New Delhi

Education

Allahabad agricultural deemed university PGDCA